<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Living on Live Average</title>
    <link>https://liveaverage.github.io/categories/living/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Living on Live Average</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://liveaverage.github.io/categories/living/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>One-person motorcycle loading</title>
      <link>https://liveaverage.github.io/news/one-person-motorcycle-loading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 14:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liveaverage.github.io/news/one-person-motorcycle-loading/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://liveaverage.com/wp-content/themes/mimbo2.2/images/BG_Package-Medium.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignleft&#34; src=&#34;http://liveaverage.com/wp-content/themes/mimbo2.2/images/BG_Package-Medium-1024x682.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BG_Package (Medium)&#34; width=&#34;257&#34; height=&#34;172&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;My wife is tiny&amp;#8230; 5 ft tiny&amp;#8230; Suffice it to say I needed a safe and easy way to load (and unload) my motorcycle without assistance. I researched the expensive solutions from LoadAll and deemed it unnecessarily complicated (with far too many moving parts) for my taste. I also didn&amp;#8217;t want to sacrifice my truck cargo space. I decided on the &lt;a title=&#34;Two different sizes, but both are plenty wide at 40 inches.&#34; href=&#34;http://www.discountramps.com/black-widow-motorcycle-ramp.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;40&amp;#8243; wide, 8 ft. long Black Widow Ramp from DiscountRamps.com&lt;/a&gt; combined with the &lt;a title=&#34;Can&#39;t go wrong with the price on this motorcycle stand/chock.&#34; href=&#34;http://www.harborfreight.com/motorcycle-stand-wheel-chock-97841.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Harbor Freight Motorcycle Stand/Wheel Chock&lt;/a&gt; (not permanently mounted &amp;#8212; temporarily secured with ratchet straps). Although I&amp;#8217;m only loading my 2007 GSXR600 (a whopping 354 lbs.) and occasionally my 2012 Hayabusa (still relatively light at 573 lbs.),  this ramp could easily handle my parents&amp;#8217; 2007 Harley FLHX Street Glide or 2012 Harley Sportster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-ramp&#34;&gt;The Ramp&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://liveaverage.com/wp-content/themes/mimbo2.2/images/BG_Load-Medium.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignright&#34; src=&#34;http://liveaverage.com/wp-content/themes/mimbo2.2/images/BG_Load-Medium-1024x682.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BG_Load (Medium)&#34; width=&#34;257&#34; height=&#34;172&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The &lt;a title=&#34;Two different sizes, but both are plenty wide at 40 inches.&#34; href=&#34;http://www.discountramps.com/black-widow-motorcycle-ramp.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;40&amp;#8243; wide, 8 ft. long Black Widow Ramp from DiscountRamps.com&lt;/a&gt; is plenty long so the incline isn&amp;#8217;t too steep, even when loading or unloading on a flat surface. It&amp;#8217;s also wide enough to accommodate load-up mishaps requiring both feet down for immediate stabilization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-chock&#34;&gt;The Chock&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, &lt;a title=&#34;Can&#39;t go wrong with the price on this motorcycle stand/chock.&#34; href=&#34;http://www.harborfreight.com/motorcycle-stand-wheel-chock-97841.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Harbor Freight&amp;#8217;s Motorcycle Stand/Wheel Chock&lt;/a&gt; is cheap and generic, but it gets the job done and I&amp;#8217;ve never had an issue with it. I can&amp;#8217;t say how it holds up to the elements since I remove it from my truck bed when not in use, but I&amp;#8217;ve never had a doubt about its ability to hold my bike steady while it&amp;#8217;s getting strapped-in for a ride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;#8217;t opt for a permanent mount solution. I couldn&amp;#8217;t bring myself to drill through the truck bed. All of the motorcycle strap support should be pulling &lt;strong&gt;down&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;forward&lt;/strong&gt; (towards the front of the truck and chock), so once the bike is IN the chock then a permanent mount isn&amp;#8217;t really necessary. I also run a strap through the rear passenger peg supports (also pulling &lt;strong&gt;down &lt;/strong&gt;and only slightly back). To secure the chock for unloading, I ran ratchet straps through its frame pulling it toward the front of the truck. This will keep things held down while you rock the bike out of the chock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-extra-mile&#34;&gt;The Extra Mile&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://liveaverage.com/wp-content/themes/mimbo2.2/images/BG_Ready-Medium.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignleft&#34; src=&#34;http://liveaverage.com/wp-content/themes/mimbo2.2/images/BG_Ready-Medium-1024x682.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BG_Ready (Medium)&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;200&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; If you still need some cargo room and some added security, consider a truck bed extender. I picked up a nice &lt;a title=&#34;Amp Truck Bed Extender&#34; href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/AMP-Research-74813-01A-Extender-2007-12/dp/B00AECRADE/ref=sr_1_7?s=automotive&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1395669075&amp;sr=1-7&amp;keywords=amp+truck+bed+extender+tundra&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Amp Research Truck Bed Extender&lt;/a&gt; from Amazon. This gives me a little extra cargo space and some added security with regard to towing (peace of mind) _and_ theft prevention. The extender can lock into your truck gate&amp;#8217;s hardware, which can then be locked with a key. Sure, somebody could cut the straps holding the extender in place, but it&amp;#8217;s one more step for a would-be thief.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix Hotbodies Slash-cut Megaphone Exhaust and Kickstand Spacing Problem</title>
      <link>https://liveaverage.github.io/features/living/fix-hotbodies-slash-cut-megaphone-exhaust-and-kickstand-spacing-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liveaverage.github.io/features/living/fix-hotbodies-slash-cut-megaphone-exhaust-and-kickstand-spacing-problem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently purchased a set of Hotbodies Slash-cut megaphone exhausts (dual) for my 2012 Suzuki Hayabusa. They sound beautiful, and other drivers are actually aware of my presence, unlike riding with the stock cans. The only issue I&amp;#8217;ve experienced is the spacing between the kickstand [in the UP position] and the LH (Driver-side) slip-on exhaust. The kickstand essentially hits the exhaust before it&amp;#8217;s in the full UP position. This also prevented the kickstand pressure safety switch from recognizing the kickstand was actually UP, resulting in stall-outs shifting into 1st gear from neutral [by design].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I contacted the manufacturer who suggested adding a spacer between the kickstand and bike, but this suggestion was useless&amp;#8230; There isn&amp;#8217;t any space between the kickstand and kickstand bracket [that mounts to the chassis]. I added spacers/washers between the kickstand bracket and chassis, but that accomplished nothing&amp;#8230; It only permitted the kickstand to hit the exhaust at a HIGHER, more noticeable contact point. Spacing the bracket/kickstand also raised concerns about adequate support for the bike when leaned over; moving it further out created more of a lean. I didn&amp;#8217;t feel comfortable pursuing this solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone on Hayabusa.org mentioned mounting/welding a nut to the kickstand nub that engages/disengages the kickstand safety switch. I ended up pursuing this, but with a bit more elegance. Parts list [obtained from Home Depot]:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cap Screw (2-pack) #8-32 x &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;&amp;#8243; Stainless Steel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonded Sealing Washers #8 Galvanized (4-pack)

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plain steel/galvanized #8 washers will do. I wanted something to seal the drilled-out hole to prevent corrosion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cap Nut (6-pack) #8-32 Zinc

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Galvanized would have been preferred, but I couldn&amp;#8217;t locate them. I needed something rounded (button-top) to slide/push-in on the safety switch. It&amp;#8217;s not perfect, but it does the job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thread-lock&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use chock and rear-stand to support the bike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove kickstand from bike. You don&amp;#8217;t need to remove the kickstand bracket, just the kickstand (one nut, one bolt, and the spring set)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using a &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;32&lt;/sub&gt; drill bit, &lt;em&gt;carefully&lt;/em&gt; drill the tab/nub on the kickstand. Use a decent bit to avoid skating/slips.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can reinstall the kickstand (recommended) or choose to install the cap screw/bolt, washers, and cap nut before you remount the kickstand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure the cap nut is installed facing up [when the kickstand is down]. This should protrude enough to engage/disengage the safety switch AND keep your kickstand from touching the exhaust.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How-to: GSX650F &amp; Vortex 41mm Clip-ons</title>
      <link>https://liveaverage.github.io/features/living/how-to-gsx650f-vortex-41mm-clip-ons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liveaverage.github.io/features/living/how-to-gsx650f-vortex-41mm-clip-ons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Author Note: I wrote this article when I still&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;owned my GSX650F. I&amp;#8217;ve since traded-up for a 2007 GSXR600 (and I couldn&amp;#8217;t be happier). I might have some images to post with this tutorial, but I&amp;#8217;ll post them when/if I can find them. Hopefully the write-up is enough to help&amp;#8230; Good luck, modders.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://liveaverage.com/wp-content/themes/mimbo2.2/images/08VortexClipOnsLG1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignleft size-thumbnail wp-image-317&#34; title=&#34;Vortex 41MM Clip-ons&#34; src=&#34;http://liveaverage.com/wp-content/themes/mimbo2.2/images/08VortexClipOnsLG1-150x150.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Vortex 41MM Clip-ons&#34; width=&#34;150&#34; height=&#34;150&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Prior to my experiences with the Suzuki GSX650F, I was the semi-proud owner of a Hyosung GT250R. I loved the body styling, aggressive riding position, cheap price ($3300 OTD) and gas mileage, but I realized something more powerful was necessary for longer trips (and riding 2-up with the Mrs.).  This brought me to my evolving 2008 GSX650F, which has the power, speed, and styling qualities that I was looking for, but still lacked the aggressive riding position I had with the Hyosung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vortex Racing had the answer to my commuter bar problem: 41mm clip-ons. They&amp;#8217;re available in three different colors: silver (aluminum), black, and gold. Additionally, Vortex manufactures after-market bar ends (weighted or unweighted) for their clip-ons &amp;#8212; which are certainly necessary after losing the dampers. The install took less than 45 minutes, but I&amp;#8217;ll admit I made the mistake of loosening one of the fork bolts &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; much while lowering the front-end (required for installation on the GSX650F). This inevitably resulted in a lopsided front after the left fork pushed right through the triple-tree clamp. An extra 10 minutes of jacking the bike up and re-adjustment was required. Here&amp;#8217;s a concise set of steps used to complete the project:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Materials:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(1) Pair of Vortex 41mm Clip-on handle bars (clamps and bars)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(1) Pair of new grips (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(1) Pair of bar-end sliders, preferably weighted (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set of allen keys/wrenches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Philips-head screwdriver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rubber mallet or lightweight hammer wrapped in cloth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Patience, maybe some coffee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove the control housings, levers, and grips from the handlebars. If one or both of your grips happen to be glued/adhered to the handlebars, you may want to remove all the control housings &amp;amp; levers first, then cut the grip(s) off with shears after the bars are away from the bike. To access the (2) phillips-head screws holding the switch housings on the bars, it may be necessary to first loosen the handlebar clamps and rotate the bar toward the front of the bike.  The levers should have two-piece clamps holding them to the bars.** Be careful when separating the throttle control housing. It may be best to loosen the housing and slide the throttle control assembly off the bar since the plastic throttle sleeve and throttle control housing are connected with cabling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When all the controls and levers are safely away from the bars (and bike body), loosen and remove the handlebar clamps using the appropriate allen wrench. Set the bars aside and re-tighten the clamps back to the triple-tree, or you may want to completely remove the clamp assembly. Your choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next you need to very carefully (and I can&amp;#8217;t stress this enough &amp;#8212; &lt;em&gt;very carefully&lt;/em&gt;) loosen the (3) fork bolts [ (1) on the triple-tree clamp, (2) above the front fender] on &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; side of the bike. It is strongly recommended to only perform this procedure on one side of the bike at a time to prevent your entire front-end from sliding down the forks (like mine!). You&amp;#8217;ll want to leave the three bolts fairly snug, then use the rubber mallet to hammer on the triple-tree clamp until the fork begins to push through the top of the triple-tree. Keep your clip-ons nearby to measure how much of the fork you&amp;#8217;ll require above the triple-tree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once the clip-on clamp gap is filled from top-to-bottom with the fork, re-tighten the (3) fork bolts to prevent the front-end from sliding. Leave the clip-on clamp loose for later adjustments (trust me, you&amp;#8217;ll be making plenty of them).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeat these same steps for the other side of the bike, making certain you don&amp;#8217;t loosen the (3) fork bolts &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; much. Again, don&amp;#8217;t over-tighten the clip-on hardware until all controls are remounted and all adjustments are made. Go ahead and tighten the the bar clamps, making sure the bars are positioned the furthest distance from the bike/tank (the black bar end near the dash should almost be under the bar clamp) .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next, begin remounting your control housings and levers onto the new clip-on bars. Don&amp;#8217;t tighten hardware completely. Instead, tighten just enough to wiggle or move the housings/levers across the bars for adjustments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now here comes the tedious step: adjustment. If you have a motorcycle jack or center stand (I don&amp;#8217;t), put the bike on it if you haven&amp;#8217;t already. You need to find the sweet-spot for clip-on positioning&amp;#8230; You should be able to cut hard-left or hard-right without pinching your hands between the bars and the tank &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; without hitting the control housings or levers on the bike&amp;#8217;s dash. Yes, it can be done. I was more worried about my hands getting pinched between the bars and tank, so my controls are &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; close (millimeters) to the dash, but they &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; clear them without rubbing or scraping.

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you don&amp;#8217;t have a jack, you&amp;#8217;ll be doing a lot of tightening/loosening and turning to test for clearance. The only constant is the &lt;em&gt;bar&lt;/em&gt; positioning on the clip-on clamps. The black, plastic bar end near the center of the dash should be as close as possible to the clamp (without actually clamping down on it).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adjust the angle of the clip-ons by rotating them around the forks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adjust the x-axis positioning of the controls by sliding them back and forth across the clip-on bars. Any scratches on the bars can generally be polished out with Mother&amp;#8217;s Aluminum polish.&lt;em&gt;NOTE: you may need to mount the plastic throttle assembly a bit more inside if you&amp;#8217;re installing bar-ends (weighted or unweighted). Otherwise, the grips (once installed) may rub on the inside of the bar-end, causing the throttle to stick (uh&amp;#8230; not good).&lt;/em&gt;  __&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adjust the y-axis positioning of the controls by rotating them up and down on the bars.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep turning the bars left and right to test for clearance, repeat as needed._** NOTE: It is extremely helpful to sit on the bike while making some of these adjustments.  It may also help to temporarily remove your cables and tubing from the cable management arm(s) to permit a more free range of movement while adjusting. Once the positioning is correct, be sure to test for adequate cable/tubing slack and safe movement when turning hard-left or hard-right.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_
  * Whenever your adjustment are complete, it&amp;#8217;s time to tighten the control housings and clip-on clamps. You may need a socket wrench with a bit adapter to tighten some of the control housing(s) due to their awkward position.
  * Lastly, install your grips (pre-existing or new) according to their instruction guide (i.e. using adhesive, soapy water, etc.). Depending on the type and style of grips, and whether or not you purchased bar-ends, you may need to cut the end-cap on the grips. I used fairly generic Pro-Grip grips that required me to cut the ends off so I could mount my Vortex bar-ends.
As mentioned elsewhere, make sure to take it slow and easy on your first ride. Turning is &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; easier (and quicker) with the new bars. Also be sure to carry a set of allen keys for any adjustments (or clamp tightening) while out on your first ride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gsx650f.biz/lowering-t915.html?highlight=triple&#34;&gt;http://www.gsx650f.biz/lowering-t915.html?highlight=triple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.squidbusters.com/sb/showthread.php?threadid=682&#34;&gt;http://www.squidbusters.com/sb/showthread.php?threadid=682&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How-to: GSX650F Chop-shop Job (Cutting down the fender)</title>
      <link>https://liveaverage.github.io/features/living/how-to-gsx650f-chop-shop-job-cutting-down-the-fender/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 16:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liveaverage.github.io/features/living/how-to-gsx650f-chop-shop-job-cutting-down-the-fender/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;Per another owner&amp;#8217;s request, here are some up-close shots of the chop-job for the 2008 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;GSX650F &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;&amp;#8230; Notice &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;the black bolts &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;(attached to the protruding box shapes beneath the fender) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;in the second image. These are holding the bracket to the bike &amp;#8216;trunk.&amp;#8217; There&amp;#8217;s a lock washer and nut on the inside of the trunk securing the bracket to the bike.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;I did not remove the tail before cutting. I used only a razor knife (with new, clean blades) following a hand-drawn [penciled] line. I did have to change the blade out about half-way through, and I did slice the crap out of a finger, but it was still worth the end-result.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plate is not actually at an angle, but if you purchased the same tail light w/ the integrated signals and plate light, you don&amp;#8217;t need it at an angle. It&amp;#8217;s clearly visible at night without bending or angled mounting. Also, you may need some additional hardware (2 X bolts, 2 X nuts, 2 X lock-washers) to re-mount the OEM plate bracket to what&amp;#8217;s left of the tail after the chop. Depending on how small your hands are, you might have to remove the tail piece (not the rear fender, just the painted tail) to attach lock-washers and nuts on the inside of the &amp;#8216;trunk&amp;#8217;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3603/3513737951_deb1a2d44c.jpg&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Figure 1) Profile view of the chop-shop job and license bracket&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3362/3513737605_cb52d3b6a7.jpg&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 2) These black bolts secure the bracket to the bike trunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3660/3513737675_c3473c91d2.jpg&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 3) No need to bend your license plate. The LEDs from the aftermarket tail-light project perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3545/3513737747_99ce71fd23.jpg&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 4) Again, view the bracket mounted to the protruding trunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;postbody&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3385/3513737785_7332e1eb7d.jpg&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Figure 5) Using a razor knife gave a perfect, clean edge. No need to sand or grind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3399/3513737883_1f06285b28.jpg&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 6) You can still see my pencil marks :S&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>