<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Motorycles on Live Average</title>
    <link>https://liveaverage.github.io/categories/motorycles/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Motorycles on Live Average</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://liveaverage.github.io/categories/motorycles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix Hotbodies Slash-cut Megaphone Exhaust and Kickstand Spacing Problem</title>
      <link>https://liveaverage.github.io/features/living/fix-hotbodies-slash-cut-megaphone-exhaust-and-kickstand-spacing-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liveaverage.github.io/features/living/fix-hotbodies-slash-cut-megaphone-exhaust-and-kickstand-spacing-problem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently purchased a set of Hotbodies Slash-cut megaphone exhausts (dual) for my 2012 Suzuki Hayabusa. They sound beautiful, and other drivers are actually aware of my presence, unlike riding with the stock cans. The only issue I&amp;#8217;ve experienced is the spacing between the kickstand [in the UP position] and the LH (Driver-side) slip-on exhaust. The kickstand essentially hits the exhaust before it&amp;#8217;s in the full UP position. This also prevented the kickstand pressure safety switch from recognizing the kickstand was actually UP, resulting in stall-outs shifting into 1st gear from neutral [by design].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I contacted the manufacturer who suggested adding a spacer between the kickstand and bike, but this suggestion was useless&amp;#8230; There isn&amp;#8217;t any space between the kickstand and kickstand bracket [that mounts to the chassis]. I added spacers/washers between the kickstand bracket and chassis, but that accomplished nothing&amp;#8230; It only permitted the kickstand to hit the exhaust at a HIGHER, more noticeable contact point. Spacing the bracket/kickstand also raised concerns about adequate support for the bike when leaned over; moving it further out created more of a lean. I didn&amp;#8217;t feel comfortable pursuing this solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone on Hayabusa.org mentioned mounting/welding a nut to the kickstand nub that engages/disengages the kickstand safety switch. I ended up pursuing this, but with a bit more elegance. Parts list [obtained from Home Depot]:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cap Screw (2-pack) #8-32 x &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;&amp;#8243; Stainless Steel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonded Sealing Washers #8 Galvanized (4-pack)

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plain steel/galvanized #8 washers will do. I wanted something to seal the drilled-out hole to prevent corrosion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cap Nut (6-pack) #8-32 Zinc

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Galvanized would have been preferred, but I couldn&amp;#8217;t locate them. I needed something rounded (button-top) to slide/push-in on the safety switch. It&amp;#8217;s not perfect, but it does the job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thread-lock&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use chock and rear-stand to support the bike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove kickstand from bike. You don&amp;#8217;t need to remove the kickstand bracket, just the kickstand (one nut, one bolt, and the spring set)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using a &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;32&lt;/sub&gt; drill bit, &lt;em&gt;carefully&lt;/em&gt; drill the tab/nub on the kickstand. Use a decent bit to avoid skating/slips.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can reinstall the kickstand (recommended) or choose to install the cap screw/bolt, washers, and cap nut before you remount the kickstand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure the cap nut is installed facing up [when the kickstand is down]. This should protrude enough to engage/disengage the safety switch AND keep your kickstand from touching the exhaust.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>